tlsbooks.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy for visitors to tlsbooks.com

Privacy Policy for visitors to tlsbooks.com.

Tlsbooks.com and its affiliates may request certain personally identifiable information for the purpose of fulfilling an order or acknowledging a donation. We will not knowingly disclose this information to others. We may also collect non-personally identifiable information for the purpose of enhancing the website experience for our visitors, compiling site statistics or supporting an activity engaged in on this website. Examples of the information we may collect and analyze include but are not limited to your Internet protocol (IP) address, name and e-mail address. We may also collect computer and connection information such as browser type and operating system. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rightsas a copyright holder and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process. We reserve the right to release any personal information we may have acquired from you in the event of unlawful activities (such as copyright infringement) or obscene or threatening actions by you. We will not send e-mail request or contact you via e-mail unless you have contacted us and would like a reply. We reserve the right to send correspondence in the case of illegal/unethical activity such as copyright infringement or bandwidth theft.

We may utilize third party vendors and/or advertisers on this site. These vendors and/or advertisers may include but are not limited to Adobe.com, PayPal.com, and Google.com. You understand that third party websites may utilize cookies and will have their own privacy and security policies. It is your responsibility to understand these policies. Tlsbooks.com may modify this privacy policy any time and you may view these terms on our website.

Update 4/7/09  
We are currently using third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (NOT INCLUDING your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [ click here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/).

The following information about Google and the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) may be of interest to our visitors:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We use cookies to improve your online experience, for analytics, for marketing,and ad presentation. Tlsbooks uses Cookies for the following purposes:

Analytical Purposes | 

We use cookies to analyze user activity in order to improve the user experience and functionality of tlsbooks.com. 

TLSBooks uses Google Analytics. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage.

By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described in [Google's Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

You may opt out of Google Analytics if you disable or refuse the cookie, disable JavaScript, or [use the opt-out service provided by Google](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).  
  
---|---  
Social Media | 

Tlsbooks may use services provided by twitter.com, pinterest.com, or facebook.com. Should you choose to interact with these services, their privacy policies apply to that interaction.

View [Twitter Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy).

View Pintrest Privacy Policy.

View [Facebook Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation).  
  
Advertising | 

Tlsbooks is funded through advertising or third-party sales generated on the website. We do not utilize pop-up or pop-under ads and believe that the ads displayed are unobtrusive and do not interfere with your use of this site.

Tlsbooks.com uses Google Adsense for advertising purposes. Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to our visitors based on their visit to his sites and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). Alternatively, you may opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

TLSBooks provides references to available items on Amazon.com that we feel may be of interest to our visitors or compliment the content on our site. View the [Amazon Privacy Policy](https://services.amazon.com/content/Privacy_Policy.html).  
  
Fraud/Spam Prevention | 

Your IP address may be used to combat copyright information, spam, or terms of use violations.  
  
Personal Information | 

We may ask for your email address or name (or you may knowingly provide us with this information) in order to respond to a comment or request from you. We do not sell, share, trade or disclose this information. All email contact is destroyed within thirty days.

We reserve the right to refrain from destroying email contact information in the case of suspected fraud, fraud, spam, or threatening or harassing behavior. In this case, you information may be retained indefinitely to support any claims of wrongdoing or harassment.  
  
Service Providers | 

TLSBooks uses the services and/or tools from the following companies to provide content or process payments through our website.

PayPal - View the [Paypal.com Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full).

Adobe - View the [ Adobe Privacy Policy](https://www.adobe.com/privacy.html).

Copyright Clearance Center - View the [Copyright Clearance Center Privacy Policy](http://www.copyright.com/about/privacy-policy/).  
  
Referral Tracking | 

We use Google Analytics and Quantcast to track referrals and learn how visitors interact with our site.

View the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

View the [Quantcast Privacy Policy](https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/).  
  
**Managing cookies in your browser**

Use the options in your web browser if you do not wish to receive a cookie or if you wish to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. You can manage or delete any cookies that have been installed in the cookie folder of your browser. These links will help you manage your cookies with popular browsers. If your borwser is not listed here, please see your instructions published by your browser manufacturer.

If you disable all cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all the features found on tlsbooks.com.
